[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "What is 5 X 5 ?",
"a": "20",
"b": "30",
"c": "32",
"d": "25",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "What is 12 + 8 ?",
"a": "18",
"b": "25",
"c": "20",
"d": "21",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "Which shape has 3 sides ?",
"a": "Square",
"b": "Retangle",
"c": "Triangle",
"d": "Circle",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "Which number comes after 99 ?",
"a": "100",
"b": "101",
"c": "98",
"d": "97",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "What is 100 ÷ 10 ?",
"a": "5",
"b": "10",
"c": "15",
"d": "20",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": "What is the square of 4 ?",
"a": "23",
"b": "15",
"c": "16",
"d": "18",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "What is 5² (5 squared) ?",
"a": "90",
"b": "24",
"c": "30",
"d": "25",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": "Which is the largest number ?",
"a": "100",
"b": "11",
"c": "1000",
"d": "2",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "Which is 3 + 6 X 2 ?",
"a": "12",
"b": "18",
"c": "15",
"d": "21",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "What is the cube root of 729 ?",
"a": "8",
"b": "9",
"c": "18",
"d": "81",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
}
]